(Bernadette:)Can we please just go back
to having a nice time?
(Amy:)We could, but unfortunately
my brain is lesion-free
(Amy:)and I remember that rotten thing
you just said about my sweet baboo.
(Bernadette:)Come on, I apologize.
Can we please just let it go?
(Amy:)-Sure.
-Thanks.
Your husbands weird
and his clothes are ridiculous.
I can't believe it! All this time
I've been doing nothing
(Penny:)but sit around and miss that guy.
And you know what the worst part is?
(Sheldon:)That you're having to process
your emotional pain without vodka?
(Scene:)No.
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Penny:)But you know what
the second-worst part is?
(Penny:)-He does not miss me at all.
-Allow me to comfort you.
(Sheldon:)At least you've got your health.
Really? That's it?
That's comforting?